all right so I have the question here
about whether you should quit your job
in order to the do the beginner boost
and the answer is
no super quick video but the answer is
no put up with the job you have keep the
money coming in use that money coming in
to buy a very cheap computer $150
optiflex separate video on that start
getting your Linux skills up maybe take
try your handed coding and do the
beginner boost at your own time and
Leisure there's no rush here as as long
as you have income right if you don't
have any income at all then it's
probably more important for you to get a
job that provides a base level income
even if it's a horrible service job
and you know then use that time and
money it's going to make you tired for
sure but on the weekend spend the time
learning the other skills that you need
um I just want to be really clear clear
here because the fact that somebody
asked a question about whether they
should quit their job and do the
beginner boost and they would become
Ultra Rich that's a mistake don't do
that